翻译　水平有限的皮带断了
汤姆 是关于韦斯达 他把公司给我了
Tom, it's Waystar. He offered it to me.
字　　幕　　侠
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
后期　Jason肖　特效　小布
做接班人
To be next.
ZIMUXIA.CN
我以为 这是我们希望
I thought that it was something that we wanted
校对　水平有限的皮带断了　时间轴　阿布
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
由我来得到的东西
for me, to have it.
压制　Jason肖
我只是计划的一个修改
Me is just a modification of the plan.
监制　水平有限的皮带断了
这是...相当大的一个修改
That's q... quite a big modification.
ZIMUXIA.CN
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
你活在阳春白雪的泡沫里 而且 你和汤姆
You live in a kind of a bubble and your connections
和泛美网络科技的关系 让你分心了
to Tom, ATN, are a distraction.
你知道吗 我不干了
Well you know what, I'm out.
我也需要在城里找个落脚点 因为我还在申请
I needed a place in the city because I'm still applying
美国总统这份工作
for the job of president of the United States.
从来没有做过任何事 从没做过
Never done nothing, never,
到现在要做世界上最重要的工作
to most important job in the world?
你怎么看待皮尔斯
What do you think about Pierce?
收购吗 皮尔斯公司
Buying? PGM?
我认为那不切实际
Think that's chasing the white whale.
开除大半个董事会 真的明智吗
Is it wise to fire the board?
别他妈不服输
Take it like a fucking man.
你想搞死我 结果弄巧成拙
You tried to kill me, but you failed.
我们需要在两天之后的投资人会议之前
We need a way forward on the Vaulter problem ahead
找到解决沃尔特公司的办法
of investor meetings in two days' time.
而且不符合我们的核心 你知道的 价值观
Doesn't fit with our core, you know, values.
所以现在我在想 直接关掉这个操蛋的公司得了
So now I'm thinking, we just shutter the fucker.
那样会让我们看起来很虚弱
I mean, it makes us look weak.
不 这会让我们看起来很无情
No, it makes us look ruthless.
你弟弟说得对 拆分吧
Your brother's right. Gut it.
恐怕我必须通知你们 你们都被解雇了
I'm afraid I have to inform you, you're all fired.
我们已经在七楼全面投入运营了
We're already fully operation on seven.
为什么
Why?
因为我爸让我这么干的
Because my dad told me to.
你做得很好 儿子
You did good, son.
请自便
Make yourself at home.
显然 写传记这事 让人望而生畏
Obviously, this is daunting, writing a biography.
对洛根·罗伊这样的人进行严肃研究 我...
A serious study of a man like Logan Roy, I...
非常感谢你同意与我见面
Thank you so much for agreeing to meet with me.
当然 但是 先说清楚 这不是会面
Sure. But just to be clear, this isn't a meeting.
这只是预见面 看看我是否愿意正式会面
This is a precursor to see if I might be willing to meet.
当然 你非常清楚自己的担忧
Absolutely. You were very clear about your concerns.
因为和你正式会面将是一大步
Because actually meeting you would be a big step.
我是一个时间紧迫的高管
I'm a time-pressed executive,
所以 在我们讨论伦理问题之前
so before we even get to the ethical considerations,
我得先看看能不能挤出我的日程
can I eke out time in my calendar?
当然
Of course.
另一方面 我...
On the other hand, I...
请不要认为我过于自我膨胀了
don't think it's too self-aggrandizing
我希望能传授一些智慧
to hope I might have some wisdom to impart.
没有比现在更好的时机了
There's no time like the present,
-对吧  - 这需要谨慎
- right? - It would need to be discreet.
我不想让我的叔公生气 因为他可能会...
I don't wanna make my uncle mad, because he can be...
好吧 他可能会很可怕 报复 偏执...
Well, he can be scary, vindictive, paranoid...
-嗯  -...暴力...
- Yeah. - ...violent...
可怕 报复...
Scary, vindictive...
等等 对不起...
Wait, I'm sorry....
不 不 不 这些都没... 我没有说这些话
No, no, no. None of this... I'm not actually saying that.
还没正式说
Yet.
你希望这次会面仅供参考吗
Would you like this meeting to be on background?
但这次不是...
But this isn't...
你不能透露我说了什么
You can't say I said anything.
但你确实说了
But you did.
听着 格雷格 如果你希望匿名
Look, Greg, if you want this to be anonymous,
你必须从一开始就声明
you have to say that from the outset.
你不能追溯回去
You can't do that retroactively.
但是不 因为这次不是会面
But no, because this isn't a meeting.
-这... 你不能...  -听着...
- This... You can't... - Look...
-这样不公平 这不公平的  -格雷格
- That's not fair. That's unfair. - Greg,
我正在写这本传记
I am writing this biography.
我将介绍洛根·罗伊的生活和工作
I am going to cover Logan Roy's life and work.
我真的毫不怀疑
And I really have no doubt
你有一堆会议要开
that you have been to a bunch of meetings,
而且你做了很多事情
and you have done a bunch of things.
所以 我的问题是
So, my question is:
你想要表达自己的观点
Do you want to present your side,
还是说 你乐于让别人告诉你他们的观点
or are you happy for everyone else to tell their version?
好的 我得思考一下 我需要... 我要走了
Okay, I need to think. I need... I'm gonna go,
我... 我... 但是我怎么离开...我长什么样
I... I'm... But this leaving... How I look,
以及我如何起床 所有的一切 都不能公开 好吗
and how I'm getting up and everything, is off the record, okay?
谢谢 女士
Thank you, ma'am.
继     承
第 二 季  第３集
那 你还是很僵硬
So you're still getting the stiffness?
脖子和肩膀 胸口还是在痛 我听说了
Neck and shoulders. Chest pains, too, I heard.
痛 一阵痛
Pain. One pain.
那是因为你让我做了那么多该死的运动
That's 'cause you've got me working out so fuckin' much.
我他妈跟约翰尼·韦斯穆勒一样黑练[奥运游泳冠军]
I'm Johnny fuckin' Weissmuller here.
我们给你的药物 嗯 你要让我知道
And the meds we've got you on, well, you let me know
如果你出现任何焦虑 偏执
if you suffer from any anxiety, paranoia,
-刺激...   -滚开
- irritation... - Fuck off.
他们试图摧毁我一生的工作
They're trying to destroy my life's work.
玛丽亚刚刚打电话说老莫的事
Maria just called about Mo.
她想知道 你想不想去临终关怀医院探访
She was wondering if you'd like to go to the hospice.
好的 我会告诉他们的
I'll let them know, yes.
我应该安排一次探访吗
Should I schedule a visit?
她说他可能只能活一两个星期了
She says he's probably only got a matter of a week or two.
不 一两个星期后再提醒我
Nah, remind me in a week or two.
还有 小西来电话了
And Shiv's on the line.
等代理权的会议开完了我再联络她
I'll do her after the proxy meet.
暂时安排到半夜
Pencil it for midnight.
我可以建议您休息一下吗
Can I suggest you look for some downtime?
今年的公司年会 你能不参与吗
Could you sit out the corporate retreat this year?
我缺席 让他们自己开会吗
Let them do the meet without me?
虽然偷腥的猫离开了 但我觉得还是不能这么干
While the cat's away, I don't fuckin' think so.
那...
So...
我们情况怎么样
how we looking?
我代表你攻城掠地
I've burned villages and overthrown governments
串谋私通
on your behalf,
我相信 只要报价合适
and I believe with the right offer,
表达正确 我们就"有机会"
correctly couched, we could be at a "maybe".
才"有机会"啊
Maybe?
怎么样
So?
休息五分钟就重新开始
Just taking five to regroup.
我现在集结了三家银行 50名律师
I've got three banks, 50 lawyers,
两个公关机构
two PR agencies,
远期市场专家
DF Kings,
和一群私家侦探试图打这场收购之战
and an army of private dicks trying to fight this takeover,
不过 花五分钟吃我的糕点 有何不可呢
but take five to eat my pastries, why don't ya?
我们实际上陷入了僵局...
We were actually at, something of an impasse...
对于我们现在真正需要的到底是不是
There were some doubts as to whether, you know,
一次收购 有些人对此有疑虑
an acquisition is really what we need right now.
正是
It is.
越大的收购越好
The bigger the better.
我志在必得
And I have it.
我们要收购PGM公司
We're going for PGM.
买下皮尔斯
Pierce.
好吧 再试一次  很...很好
Okay. Again. G... Great.
-这想法太棒了  -很好很棒
- That's chunky. - Nice and chunky.
我们利用杠杆资金 吃掉皮尔斯
We leverage up and eat Pierce,
这样 对于桑迪和斯图威来说 我们就太大了 他们吃不下
we're too big for Sandy and Stewy to come for.
他们会他妈的噎死
They'd fucking choke.
这招有可能很绝
Could be a great move.
这是个有趣的挑战
It's an, interesting challenge,
因为上一次我们尝试收购时 他们的代理人
because last time we tried it, their surrogates
称我们为"文化破坏者"
called us "cultural vandals",
和"公共话语源泉中的毒药"
and "poison in the well of public discourse".
嗯...
Well...
时代变了
times have changed.
我...我不想说太多
I... I don't wanna say too much.
某些年轻的表兄弟想要钱买游艇吗
Some of the young cousins want yacht money?
好吧 这... 很微妙
Well, it's... it's delicate,
就像法国人亲吻犰狳一样
like French kissing an armadillo.
我们要他妈的吃掉他们
We're gonna fucking eat them up.
-好吗  -好的 我们开干吧
- Good? - Yeah. Let's do it.
-我喜欢这点子  -滚开 老哥
- I like it. - Fuck off, dude.
不要这么擦鞋好吗 太可悲了
Don't be such a suck-up. It's pathetic.
你觉得怎么样 罗慕路斯
What about you, Romulus?
我他妈的喜欢这点子 但是这是我的真实意见
I fucking love it, but that's my honest opinion.
好 开干 赶紧
Great. Forward. Fast.
大家都喜欢这个计划吧
We all like this?
皮尔斯...
Pierce...
为什么他总是回到这个话题
Why does he keep coming back to this?
我只是... 你知道 我想搞明白
I just... You know, I wanna understand.
因为这是个力量倍增器
Because it's a force multiplier.
一个行业 很多品牌
One sector, many brands.
此外 PGM基本上收购了就能派上用场
Plus PGM is basically plug and play for us.
是的 是的 是的 因为尤恩叔叔看这个台
Yeah, yeah, yeah. It's 'cause Uncle Ewan watches it.
这是他最喜欢的新闻频道 所以爸想​​要买它
It's his favorite news, so Dad wants to buy it
-为了让尤恩叔叔生气  -什么 花200亿为了这
- to piss him off. - What, for 20 billion?
好吧 他就不能直接从遥控器里取掉电池吗
Well, can't he just take the batteries out of his remote?
好吧 皮尔斯还拥有纽约邮报
Well, Pierce also own the New York Mail,
我们都他妈讨厌邮报
and we fucking hate the Mail.
洛根借了许多古希腊军事文物
Logan loaned a number of ancient Greek military artifacts
給盖蒂别墅博物馆 并举行了酒会
to the Getty Villa, and held a drinks reception.
邮报刊登了一篇轰动一时的文章
The Mail did a hit piece.
他们说他上的白葡萄酒是温热的
They said he served warm white wine,
还说他以为柏拉图是马克思兄弟之一[美国喜剧团体]
and that he thought Plato was one of the Marx brothers.
为了报复那四英寸宽的小新闻
And to avenge that four inches of newsprint,
我们正在掷骰子 赌一场200亿美元的冒险
we are rolling the dice on a 20-billion-dollar crapshoot.
所以...
So...
好的 我的意思是 是的 如果有疑问 那就...
Okay, I mean, yeah. If there are doubts, let's...
公开说出来
let's air them.
-不 我...   -因为你说得对
- No, I... - Because you're right,
如果这样的收购导致的债务
if the debt from an acquisition like this
变得无法控制 我们可能会陷入死亡螺旋
became unmanageable, we could death-spiral,
然后 我们就会和船一起沉到海底
and then, we'd all go down with the ship.
这对我们所有人来说...
It would be a reputational and financial...
将是声誉和财务上的灾难 对吗
disaster for all of us. Right?
你在说什么 肯
What are you saying, Ken?
不 我只是在判断大家的态度
No, I'm just gauging the room.
不 尽管如此 还是非常令人兴奋
No, it's nonetheless extremely exciting.
是啊 不 不 我... 我... 我喜欢这计划
Yeah. No, no. I... I... I like it.
-很好  -很好
- Good. - Good.
好吧 好 很好
Okay. Good. Great.
那我们... 那我们把这头大象给我爸搞定
Let's...Let's bag this elephant for Dad.
是啊 我们开干吧
Yeah. Let's do it.
是啊 我们把这只火鸡的骨头拆了
Yeah. Let's bone this turkey.
所以 皮尔斯就是答案
So, Pierce is the answer.
那些贵族混蛋
Those blue-blooded fucks.
商业答案 靠他们接管防守
The business answer. They take over defense.
就是这样 接下来怎么做
It's the whole thing. So what's next?
最难的部分是和这个家族联系
The tough part is contact with the family.
我们需要一个经验老手
We need a pair of safe hands.
灵巧的手 戴着精致的手套
Dainty hands, in exquisite mittens.
谁是我们里面最聪明理智的
Who's our most pointy-headed fuck?
好吧 说来惭愧...
Well, it's a shame...
不过 你确实有一个他们喜欢的重量级人物
But you did have one heavyweight that they liked.
老博尔·维达尔
Old Bore Vidal.
是啊 他们都喜欢他妈的弗兰克·莎士比亚
Yeah. They all love fucking Shakespeare Frank.
背后捅刀子的家伙
Backstabber.
什么 弗兰克吗
What? Frank?
是的 他妈的没错
Yeah fuckin' right!
爸爸 不
Dad, no.
弗兰克确实有些朋友
Frank does have friends in dry places.
他和南·皮尔斯 娜奥米都很亲近
He's close to Nam Pierce, Naomi.
你觉得他会回来吗
You think he'd come back?
是的 也许吧
Yeah, maybe.
他对权力很饥渴 痴迷于地位
He's power-hungry and status-obsessed,
而且 你知道的 贪得无厌
and, you know, avaricious,
-所以  -他还是你的教父
- so... - And pretty much your godfather,
-和你最亲密的生意...   -这些只是事实
- and your closest business... - Those are just facts.
这是他妈的胡说八道 天啦
This is fuckin' bullshit. Jesus Christ.
我觉得他知道自己做得不好
I think he knows he did bad.
他妈的 爸爸 我对天发誓
Fuck. I swear to God, Dad,
如果你让他回来公司 我就转身闪人
if you bring him back, I am walking.
闪回我的办公室...
Back to my office to...
-生闷气 他妈的  -很好
- sulk. Fuck! - Fine.
反正我他妈也不在乎
I don't fuckin' care.
公司年会的嘉宾
Guest of fucking honor at the retreat.
我们来试试吧 好吗
Let's try it. Good?
公司年会 你... 你还想去吗
Corporate retreat? You... You still wanna do that?
-你不想... 休整一下吗  -不 这可是士气助推器
- You don't wanna... hunker? - Nah. It's a morale booster.
-在哪里举行  -匈牙利
- Where is it? - Hungary.
还是那里啊
Still.
在我们达成就战略达成一致之前 这将使高层保持紧密的联系
It'll keep the top team tight till we agree on a strategy.
-不许泄漏出去  -好的
- No leaks. - Okay.
洛根...
Logan...
我是康纳
it's Connor.
我开牧场 我骑马 我赚钱 我付出
I ranch, I ride, I earn, and I give.
跟你一样
Just like you.
但是... 叮咚 是谁呀 是山姆大叔
But... ding-dong, who's there? Uncle Sam.
他的手在哪儿
And where's his hand?
在我的裤子里
In my pants.
嘿 家里有人吗
Hey, is anyone in my house?
嘿 你看这个了吗
Hey. Have you seen this?
看了
Yeah.
他说他正在测试
He said he's beta testing it,
在发照片墙和切入主要思想之前
before he Instagrams and enters the "ideas primary".
也许他是个天才
Maybe he's a genius.
只是一方面
That's one word for it.
天才牧场主
A genius rancher.
我想要的只是一个公平 统一的税收 所有美国人都一样
All I want is a fair, flat tax, same for all Americans,
但是 在十年左右的时间内降到零
but headed down to zero within a decade or so.
我该怎么办 好吧 我会告诉你
What am I gonna do? Well, I'll tell ya.
-我根本不交  -我的天啦
- I ain't paying. - My God.
如果你想逮捕我 请继续
And if you want to arrest me, go ahead.
不 真的 请直接来逮捕我
No, really. Just go ahead and try.
有个小问题
Quick question.
你认为他知道什么是监狱吗
Do you think he even knows what a jail is?
他只是从大富翁游戏中才知道的
He literally only knows it from Monopoly.
他不会真的把这个说出去
He's not actually gonna put this out there,
对吧
is he?
我想爸爸已经很生气了
I think Dad's all over it.
不过 我有一个问题要问你
I have a question for you, though.
你和... 你和娜奥米·皮尔斯是闺蜜 对吧
You're...You're pals with Naomi Pierce, right?
是啊 怎么了
Yeah. Why?
爸爸想收购PGM公司
Dad wants to buy PGM.
皮尔斯
Pierce.
但是 肯定不允许卖的
But that wouldn't be allowed.
对吧
Would it?
我的意思是 我... 我父母就看这个台
I mean that's what... My parents watch that.
播的新闻感觉很真实
That's like actual news.
他想干什么就他妈干什么
He can do whatever the fuck he likes.
他就像沙特阿拉伯的土豪
He's like a human Saudi Arabia.
那 怎么 你... 你想通过娜奥米来促成交易吗
So, what, you... you wanna use Naomi to broker a deal?
恭喜你猜中了
Bingo.
而且我认为这是一个很好的计划
And I think it's a good plan.
我达成协议...
I land the deal...
... 我干掉肯德尔 我加冕为王
...I kill Kendall. I'm crowned the king.
就像哈姆雷特里面一样
Just like in Hamlet.
如果哈姆雷特里面是这样写的话 我不在乎
If that happens in Hamlet. I don't care.
-哈姆雷特里面是这样写的  -好的
- Just like Hamlet. - Okay.
这是娜奥米的...
Here is Naomi's...
...地址
...address.
她很酷 我想你们每个人都会喜欢她
She's cool. I think you'd like her.
是吗
Yeah?
话说 你怎么认识她的
How do you know her, anyway?
你和她上床了
You fucked her.
还有没有你没有睡过的人
Is there anybody you haven't fucked?
你
You.
爸 嘿 终于打来了
Dad. Hey. Finally.
你好
Hello.
在享受你的停工期吗
Enjoying your downtime?
我正在重读10-K表格[上市公司年度报表]
I'm re-reading the 10-K.
我们需要谈谈皮尔斯
We need to talk about Pierce.
这个话题应该是保密的 谁告诉你的
That's not to be spoken of. Who told you?
我不该知道吗
Am I not supposed to know?
嘿 我在想 我们或许应该想一个
Hey, I was thinking, we should maybe think of
我在公司年会上出现的理由
a reason for me to be on the retreat,
以防我们要谈论策略
in case we're talking strategy.
听着
Listen.
我需要你去看看康纳
I need you to go and see Connor.
怎么 我现在是康纳的保姆了吗
What, I'm Connor's babysitter now?
你失业了 这是一份工作
You're unemployed. This is a job.
他可能会伤害到我们
He could hurt us.
偷税漏税之后可不会大肆宣扬
You don't go shouting about tax.
我们自有安排
We have arrangements.
等我回来的时候我们再聊
We'll talk when I'm back,
-好吗  -爸 我...
- okay? - Dad, I...
-嘿  -嗨 他妈的发生什么事了
- Hey. - Hi. What the fuck is happening?
你知道收购皮尔斯的事吗
Do you know about chasing Pierce?
当然 我他妈参会了
Sure, I was in the fucking meeting.
你怎么知道皮尔斯的事
How do you know about Pierce?
我打电话给格丽了
I had Gerri on the phone.
她认为爸已经不理性了 我同意
She thinks Dad's gone woo-woo and I agree.
你爸告诉你最新情况了吗
Did your dad update you?
这真是一场灾难 谁都说了些啥
This is a disaster. Who said what,
-谁想阻止收购  -我觉得这计划可能会很好
- and who wants to stop it? - I think it could be good.
是啊 收了皮尔斯[直译为鸡鸡比皮尔斯的大]
Yeah. Dick over Pierce,
再收了桑迪和斯图威 我们规模就翻倍了
dick over Sandy and Stewy, double our size.
没有人会想去招惹一条全身都是大鸡鸡的
No one is gonna wanna tackle a big angry puffer fish
怒气冲冲的大河豚
bristling with dick.
汤姆 这是精神不正常 这是一种痴迷
Tom, it's batshit. It's an obsession.
-什么  - 你能想象到后座力有多大吗
- What? - Can you imagine the blowback?
我们想收购皮尔斯 新闻界最受人尊敬的名字
Us trying to buy Pierce, the most respected name in news?
但是我们已经做了新闻 对吗 所以 这只是更多新闻频道而已
But we already do news, right? So it's just more news.
这就像合并效果...
It's like synergies...
是的 但是如果所有的新闻频道都是我们的
Yeah, but if we own all the news,
我确实想知道 我他妈该在哪里看我想看的新闻
I do actually wonder where I'll get my fucking news.
因为某些时候 确实有人需要
Because at some point, someone needs to actually
去跟踪世界上正在发生的事情
keep track of what's going on in the world.
谁去了哪里 谁戴了帽子
Who went where, and who wore a hat.
我认为这会是一个独立的品牌
I think it's gonna be a separate brand.
就像"让我保持真实"的燕麦品牌
Let me keep the truthy, oatmeal branding.
是的 但是美利坚共和国现在的状况并不好
Yeah, but the American Republic is in not great shape as it is.
想想看 有... 时代周刊 华盛顿邮报
What, you've got the... The Times, The Post,
皮尔斯的编辑
editors at Pierce,
推特上还有几百名愤怒的年轻女性
and a couple of hundred angry young women on Twitter,
就这些了
and that's about it.
-别这样说  -不 汤姆
- Please. - No! Tom,
已经他妈的够陈旧乏味了
it is thread-fucking-bare out there,
现在我们还要吃掉另外一个
and now we're gonna eat another one?
那 你想把这些话告诉他吗
Well, do you want to tell him that?
汤姆 这很严肃
Tom, this is serious.
这是蛇吞象
It's a snake eating a crocodile.
不合适 太大了
It doesn't fit, it's too big.
这是一笔200亿美元的收购
It's a 20-billion-dollar acquisition
要么害我们破产 要么需要花费五年时间来整合
that either breaks us or takes half a decade to integrate.
我们得阻止他
We need to stop him.
所以 在匈牙利和他谈谈
So, talk to him in Hungary.
-什么  -是的
- What? - Yeah.
我...我觉得我不想这样做 小西
I... I don't think I wanna do that, Shiv.
...喂 是复制部吗
...Hello? Is this the replicant department?
是这样的 我的人肉傀儡停止工作了
Yeah, my meat-puppet has stopped working.
小西 小西
Shiv. Shiv.
汤姆 我在开玩笑
Tom, I'm joking.
但是我也很认真
But I'm also not.
人们最好记住
People would do well to remember
有一天 镇上会有一个新警长
there's gonna be a new sheriff in town one day.
所以 召集反抗力量吧
So, rally the resistance,
副警长先生
Deputy.
嘿 格丽 为什么选择匈牙利开年会
Hey, Gerri, what's the thinking behind Hungary?
那里是个玩射击的好地方 而且 没人在乎你射中了什么
It's a nice place to shoot a gun where no one cares what you hit.
好了 伙计们 听着
So, guys, listen.
我有一个很棒的喝酒游戏 可以在飞机上玩
I have a great drinking game for the flight.
任何时候谁说皮尔斯 就喝一口
Any time he says Pierce, take a sip.
你带了自己的啊 超级水枪吗
You brought your own? Super soaker?
-是的  -我也拿了自己的 巴索猎枪
- Yep. - I got my own. Blaser.
我不想参加比谁的鸡鸡大的比赛[火力猛]
I don't wanna get into a dick-measuring competition,
但是我的枪比你的好 火力更猛
but I have a better, more powerful dick than you.
当然 我很确定这并不能说明什么
Which I'm sure isn't saying much.
肯 你跟我一起
Ken. You're with me.
我们谈谈时间表
Let's talk timetables.
我不敢相信 我... 在坐私人飞机
I can't believe I'm a... on a private plane.
就像我是乐队成员一样
It's like I'm in a band.
一个非常白人 非常有钱的...
A very white, very wealthy...
乐队
band.
就像我在U2乐队一样
It's like I'm in U2.
欢迎来到圣殿内部
Welcome to the inner-sanctum.
是啊 是的 这... 很好
Yeah. Yeah, it's... it's nice.
比圣殿外面好多了
Way nicer than the outer-sanctum.
好吧 我希望你喜欢红酒和打猎
Well, I hope you like red wine and killing shit.
-... 关于...   -什么...
- ...about the... - What...
他妈的为什么说悄悄话
What the fuck's the whispering?
恐怕卡罗丽娜有坏消息 关于那本书
Carolina has bad news, I'm afraid. On the book.
你的传记
The biography.
我告诉过你停手
I told you to stop it.
我知道 对不起
I know. I'm sorry.
我们说的很清楚 不会和她合作 但是...
We were very clear there'll be no co-operation, but...
我不希望这书发表
I don't want it to come out.
好的... 明白了
Okay... Got it.
但是 它... 它会发表
Well, it... it will come out.
在这个国家 实际上可悲的是
I can't actually, in this nation, yet,
我不能让一本书停止出版
sadly, halt the publication of a book.
可以 我们可以
Yeah, we can.
好吧 我们可以威胁她 骚扰她
Well, we can threaten and harass,
我们可以恐吓那些
we can intimidate names
可能合作的人 冒一点险
who might cooperate and get a little dicey.
动用一切手段
Everything.
那个作家 潘特西尔
The writer, Pantsil.
我们能不能让她在接下来的十年里给我们写一部电影
Can we not get her writing us a movie for the next decade?
-缜密调查她  -交给我们办
- Tooth comb her. - Leave it with us.
任何跟她访谈的人都会完蛋
Anyone who speaks to her is fucked.
他们对我来说已经死了
They're dead to me.
谁他妈也不能刺探我的隐私
No one goes sniffing round my fucking panties.
但是 恐怕就像她的朋友暗示的那样
Well, I'm afraid that what her friend has
她已经见过你身边的某些人了
suggests that she's met with someone close to you already.
-谁  -这个 我们也不知道
- Who? - Well, we don't know.
但是 是内部的人
But someone inside.
-肯 是你吗  -是我吗
- Ken, is it you? - Is it me?
爸 拜托 老天啊
Dad. Come on. Jesus.
嗯 只是 从以往的历史来看
Well, it's just, historically speaking,
当我被人背叛 通常都是你
when I'm betrayed, it's usually you.
我在开玩笑 儿子 我在开玩笑
I'm kidding, son. I'm kidding.
我可以让山姆去调查
I can get Sam on it.
去找技术人员 梳理电子邮件 公司通话记录 嗯
Go to IT, comb emails, company phones. Yep.
他妈的
Fuck!
他妈的鼠辈[内奸]
Fucking rats.
鼠辈
Rats!
那边发生什么事了
What's going on in there?
有人打算写爸爸的传记
Somebody's trying to write Dad's biography.
嘘... 这样啊
Sh... Okay.
我还没有听说 很... 很有意思
I hadn't heard. That's... That's interesting.
他不喜欢搞传记这一套...
He's not a fan of the old, the old biographical...
是的 他不喜欢
Yeah, he's not a fan.
而且 看上去有人开过口了
And, seems like somebody talked.
好吧
Okay.
那就糟糕了
That's bad.
所以 是的 有人开口了 我们内部的人
So, yeah. Someone talked. Someone inner-circle.
那边那个山姆 会把这些人揪出来
Sam over there will, smoke 'em out,
然后 爸会把他们大卸八块
and, Dad's gonna chop them up
然后扔进他妈的多瑙河里面
and throw them into the fucking Danube.
对的
Right.
蓝色多瑙河将猩红一片 不再蓝色
Blue Danube no more.
那是因为... 我在一间狩猎小屋里
That's because... I'm at a hunting lodge.
皮尔斯的计划 我们可以开始推动了吗
Pierce. We can start to push?
这么急 会有点咄咄逼人
Well, that would be pushy.
呵呵 防守太慢是没有用的
Well, too slow is no defense.
但是 太快的话 我们会惊到他们
Well, too fast and we spook 'em.
这真的太...
This is just...
我的天啊
Mon dieu!
很棒 对吧
Nice, right?
对士气很有帮助
Good for the morale.
-你的士气如何  -很好
- How's your morale? - Great.
- 我们很开心  -很好
- We're very happy. - Good.
我希望我的顶尖人才们专注皮尔斯收购计划
I want my top minds on Pierce.
我要在三明治里加些肉
I'm gonna need some meat in the sandwich.
你们可以为我做到吧 顶尖人才们
You can do that, top minds?
-可以的  -好的
- You got it. - Yeah.
还好吗
Good?
嗯 还好
Good. Yeah.
-给你 - 好的 好的 太好了
- Here you go. - Good, good, good. Great.
你好
Hello.
这里是惩罚打人的地方吗
Is this the right place for the punishment beating?
弗兰克 你好吗 过来 你这个老混蛋
Frank! How ya been? Come here, you old bastard!
快过来
Come on!
肯德尔 东西在哪
Kendall, where's the thing?
我去拿
Yeah.
对不起 我们在婚礼上没有机会聊聊 但是...
I'm sorry we didn't get a chance to speak at the wedding, but...
我们遇见四次 你根本没正眼瞧我
You must have cut me dead four times.
忙 忙 忙 一直忙
Busy, busy, busy.
-肯德尔 东西在哪  -嗯 在这
- Kendall, the thing. - Yeah, here it is.
弗兰克
Frank.
-送给你  -这是什么
- For you. - What's this?
后面 看后面
The back, the back.
"还有那高贵的事业在等待着我们
"Some work of noble note may yet be done,
只有敢与神斗的人 才能斗胆一试"
not unbecoming men who strove with gods."
很好 这礼物很棒
That's nice. It's a nice thing.
你还好吗
You okay?
桑迪和斯图威已经捏住了我的蛋蛋
Sandy and Stewy have got my nuts in a vice.
但是弗兰克 你拥有让我脱困滑出来的油脂
But Frank, you've got the grease to slip them out.
-对吧  -这一幕太让我作呕了
- Right? - Truly revolting image.
-嘿 小肯  -很高兴见到你 弗兰克
- Hey, Kenny. - Good to see you, Frank.
弗兰克
Frank.
没有你 情况就不一样了
It's not been the same without you.
变得更好了
It's been better.
-我逗你呢  -好吧
- I'm fucking with you. - Okay.
我...在开玩笑呢 先生
I'm... I'm kidding, sir.
先生们 是时候换衣服了
Gentlemen, time to change.
-我们的安全简报  -还有安全简报
- Our safety briefing. - Safety briefing?
以下是安全简报
Here's the safety briefing:
如果你们谁反对我
If you move against me,
我他妈会在你的头上轰一个洞
I'll put a hole in the back of your fucking head.
康纳
Connor?
嘿
Hey!
-嘿  -你来了啊
- Hey! - There you are.
-我来了 你好  -嗨
- Here I am. Hi. - Hi.
-这是什么  -就这个嘛
- What's this? - ...You know.
好的 谢谢 嘿 听着 跟我来
Okay, thank you. Hey, listen. Come with me.
我希望你见见我的顾问
I want you to meet my consultants.
当然 你认识埃里克·舒尔曼和巴德·亨利
You know Eric Schulman and Bud Henley, of course.
-他们加入了团队  -埃里克
- They've joined the team. - Eric.
-嘿  -都是很棒的人
- Hey. - Good guys.
-你看过了视频吗  -是的
- You saw the vid? - Yeah.
嘿 康纳...
Hey, Connor...
他们都是干正事的人 他们都他妈很牛逼
Those are serious guys. They're fuckin' pieces of shit.
是的 现在是我的牛逼手下了
Yep. They're my pieces of shit.
威拉完成了剧本重写 你想喝点什么吗
Willa's finishing up a re-write. Would you like a drink?
-不用了 我不喝 谢谢  -好的
- No. I'm good. Thanks. - Okay.
冰沙...冰沙里有什么
What's...What's in the smoothie?
勃艮第[红酒]
Burgundy.
-你说什么  -我超级醒酒[用搅拌机]
- I'm sorry? - I hyper-decant.
你不是超级醒酒吗
You don't hyper-decant?
你只是常规的醒酒方式吗
You're just doing regular decanting?
如果你说的常规醒酒方式
If by regular decanting you mean
指的是倒进我张开的嘴里 那没错了
pouring into my open mouth, yeah.
你应该用超级醒酒方式
You should hyper-decant.
能软化单宁 加重香气
It softens the tannins. Heightens the aromas.
您可以在十秒钟之内让你的葡萄酒陈酿五年
You can age your wine five years in ten seconds.
真的
Truly.
康纳...
Connor...
你知道他们是怎么对付监狱里的有钱人吗
You know what they do to rich people in jail.
知道 他们提前让有钱人出狱
Yes, they let them out early
以降低诉讼风险
to mitigate the risk of litigation.
进监狱可不是件好事
Going to jail is not a good look.
没有哪个坐监的人去竞选总统
Not many campaign posters use mugshots.
小西 世界已经变了
The world has changed, Shiv.
旧秩序摇摇欲坠
The old shibboleths are crumbling.
你知道吗 精英们很害怕
And you know what? The elites are scared.
我能看到他们在那里
I can see 'em down there,
苦苦挣扎 重新配置
a-scrabbling and reconfiguring,
而且丝毫不知道他们激起的旋风预兆着什么
with no clue what the whirlwind they have stirred heralds.
你觉得 如果你俯视这些精英
Do you think that maybe if you're looking down
比如 从这个顶层公寓俯视他们
on the elites from, like, you know, this penthouse,
也许这暗示了什么呢
maybe it's indicative of something?
聪明
Smart.
我的小妹妹很聪明 对吗
My baby sister is smart, right?
-是啊 嘿  -嗨
- She is. Hey. - Hi.
-你好吗  -是的 康纳
- How are you? - Yeah. Connor,
不要发布视频 好吗 拜托
don't release the video. Okay? Please?
为什么呢
Why?
这个家庭 我们担心你会让我们蒙羞
The family. We're worried you're gonna humiliate us,
让你自己蒙羞
and humiliate yourself.
-好的 爸说的吗  -是的
- Okay. Dad? - Yeah.
爸想阻止我
Dad wants to stop me.
好吧 告诉他去贝索斯和克林顿夫妇后面排队吧
Well, tell him to get in line behind Bezos and the Clintons.
康纳 算我求你了
Connor, I'm asking a favor.
求你了
Please.
那 我还个价怎么样
Well, how about I make counter-offer?
我有一个不太得体的提议[Indecent Proposal 电影"桃色交易"]
I'd like to make a rather indecent proposal.
我猜...我猜你还没看过这部电影吧
I'm g... guessing you haven't seen that film.
他看过 是的 这是他最喜欢的电影
He has. Yeah, it's his favorite.
我碰巧知道你闲着没事做
I happen to know you're at a loose end.
小西 来为我工作
Shiv, come and work for me.
什么 才不呢
What? No.
不 不
No. No.
这是一个千载难逢的机会 千载难逢
It's a big offer. Big.
千载难逢的机会 小西 你来负责整个竞选
Big offer, Shiv. You'd run the whole shebang.
你看 如果吉尔解雇了你 也许你
And look, if Gil fired you, maybe you're,
-现在很难找到新的工作  -他没有解雇我
- a difficult hire right now. - He didn't fire me.
-是我自己辞职的  -好吧
- I walked out. - Okay.
-我...我...   -没关系 好吗
- I... I... - No. Okay.
那要怎么样你才会改变主意呢
So what would it take for you to change your mind?
把我脑子切了
A lobotomy.
而且 要现代政治全面重组
And a total realignment of modern politics.
那个...康纳 那个视频太烂了
The... Connor, the video is batshit.
好吧
Okay.
我会和我的团队一起考虑下
I will consider with my team.
-好的  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
伙计们 我先离开五分钟
Guys, I need five.
我一会回来 然后我们再拍视频
I'll come back and we'll shoot the shit.
嘿 你对...
Hey, what's...
你对此有什么看法
What's your read on this?
对不起 我... 我...
Sorry, I... I...
我得走了 我正要去和演员们喝一杯
I have to go. I'm meeting my cast for drinks.
好吧 听起来很有趣
Okay. That sounds fun.
是啊 是的 我的意思是
Yeah. Yeah, I mean,
基本上就是一群演员
it's basically just a bunch of actors,
你知道的 在一个烂酒吧里瞎逼逼
you know, bitching in a shitty bar.
-我可以...  -什么
- Can I...- What?
你想去吗
You wanna come?
嗯 是的 你知道 我很乐意做
Well, yeah. You know, I'd love an audience
未来的第一夫人的观众
with the future first lady.
好吧 好啊 走吧
Okay. Yeah. Come on.
-你还好吗  -是的
- You okay there? - Yeah.
这很棒啊
This is nice.
欧洲
Europe.
饱受战争
Nice bit of war-torn,
鬼魂
spooky,
反犹太主义 吸血鬼 专制摧残的欧洲
anti-Semitic, vampirey, authoritarian Europe.
是啊
Yeah.
嘿 格雷格 很高兴见到你 伙计
Hey, Greg, it's good to see you, man.
你花了这么多时间和肯德尔一起玩
You're spending so much time hanging out with Kendall,
女孩子可能会开始怀疑你的性取向了
a girl could start to wonder.
不 不 不
No. No. No.
听着...那...我... 我可以问你一件事吗
Listen....So... Yeah, c... can I ask you something?
以...以朋友的身份
On the... On the friend level?
可以啊 你在担心你们在游轮上做的那些事吗
Yeah. You worried about what you did in Cruises?
我们做的那些事 ....不 不
What we did? No. No....
不 我是打算问你关于山姆的事
No. I was gonna ask you about this Sam guy.
-你认识他吗  -狗日的密探山姆 是的 当然
- Do you know him? - Rat-fucker Sam? Yeah, sure.
你知道吗 我开始约会小西之前
You know he background-checked me
他查了我的背景
before I started dating Shiv?
是啊 那 他的... 他是...
Yeah. So, what's his... Is he...
比如 他有些什么能力
Like, what's his competency?
他... 他人好吗
Is he... Is he nice?
他人好吗 你是在问一个叫"狗日的密探山姆"的
Is he nice? You're asking about the moral character
道德品格吗
of a man named Rat-fucker Sam?
他就是他妈的狗屎 他就是他妈的这样的人
He is a fucking piece of fucking shit, is what he is.
没错 怎么了 格雷格
Yeah. What's up, Greg?
我们一起经历不少事 对吧
We've been through a bit, right?
我能相信你吗
Can I trust you?
是 你当然可以相信我
Yes. Of course you can trust me.
在每方面都能相信我
To a point, yes.
那 你知道 洛根非常生气
So, you know how Logan's mad
因为有人和他的传记作者谈过话
someone talked to his biographer?
-格雷格  -所以...
- Greg. - So...
我想知道 山姆找到这个
I'm wondering how likely it is
通过私人邮箱发送电子邮件的人
that Sam will find out the person emailed
-几率有多大  -我操 伙计 竟然是你啊
- from a private email. - Fuck, man. Really?
我甚至没有和她正式会面 我没有...我只是和她预见面了
I didn't even meet her. I didn't... I pre-met her.
她... 她想把预见面变成正式会面
She... She tried to turn the pre-meet into a meet-meet,
所以我离开了
so I left.
好吧 好吧 噢 我的...
Okay, well. oh My...
如果你...如果你告诉洛根
If you... If you tell Logan,
他可能会杀了你
he might kill you.
好吗 所以你得把这事保密 伙计
Okay, so you need to put that in the locker, man,
不要告诉任何人
and don't tell anyone.
而且祈祷你可以相信我
And pray that you can trust me,
因为你刚刚给了我一个宝贵的资产
'cause you just handed me a valuable piece of capital.
格雷格
Greg!
兄弟 永远不要相信任何人 永远
Buddy. Trust no one, ever.
好吧 睿智之言
Okay. Wise words.
不 没有我在这里
No, not having me here,
刚刚离开...离开沙发
just being out of... out of the desert.
是啊
Yeah.
嘿 我能请你帮个忙吗 关于老康的
Hey, can I ask you a favor, about Con?
当然可以
Sure thing.
你能不能 让他在那段视频的事情上踩刹车
Could you maybe get him to pump the brakes on that video?
实际上 就是整个
And actually just the whole
想当自由世界的领袖这件事都踩刹车
wanting to be the leader of the free world thing?
他确实喜欢那个视频 我...
He does love a project. I...
是啊 不 我知道 但...
Yeah. No, I know, but...
我的意思是 你很聪明 你... 懂世事
I mean, you're smart. You're... worldly.
-你明白的  -好的
- You get it. - Okay.
我的意思是 我觉得那个视频没问题 不过...
I mean, I thought it looked okay, but...
你和老康 你... 我的意思是 你赞成 对吧
And you and Con, you're... I mean, you're okay, right?
这...这整个...
It's... This whole...
当然 我的意思是 我们支持彼此的梦想
Sure. I mean, we support each other's dreams.
他的梦想是白宫
His dream is the White House.
我的是百老汇
Mine is Broadway.
好吧 你知道他请的那些人
Well, you realize those guys that he's got in there,
都是些狠角色吧
those are serious guys.
我的意思是 他们会从老康身上榨取一千万
I mean, they'll suck ten million from him,
他甚至都不会意识到钱没了
and he won't even realize it's gone.
你的剧本才花多少钱
And how much is your play gonna cost?
好的 我会考虑一下
Okay, I'll think about it.
我会的 谢谢 小西
I will. Thank you, Shiv.
-威拉  -嗨 很高兴见到你
- Willa. - Hi! Good to see you.
还有你 你好 我是克里斯
And you. Hi. Chris.
小西
Shiv.
那你呢 小西
And you, Shiv?
-我  -是的
- Me? - Yeah.
你还好吗 你快乐吗 平静吗 一切都好吗
Are you okay? You're happy, calm, everything?
是啊 是啊 他妈的 是的
Yeah. Yeah. Fuck, yeah.
我想要的一切我都有
I got everything I could want.
真棒
Great.
干杯
Cheers.
嘿
Hey.
你找到机会说了吗
还没 在打猎 很难找到机会
有什么消息吗
你扛着步枪的样子看起来很棒
You look good with a rifle.
你怎么样 兄弟
How you doin', man?
你呢
You?
我想我的人正在处理野猪
I think my guy's working for the boar.
嘿 听着 我有个问题
Hey, so listen, I have a question.
仅限于你我
Between us,
你接过那位传记作者的电话了吗
did you get a call from that biographer?
我的意思是 是的 很显然 我很引人注目
I mean, yeah, obviously. I'm the interesting one.
你呢
You?
是啊
Yeah.
接到了
你在考虑和她谈谈吗
You thinking of talking to her?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许吧
Maybe.
你呢
What about you?
不 我的意思是...
No. I mean...
如果你要跟她谈谈 我想我也得跟她谈谈
If you're gonna talk to her, I guess I have to talk to her,
那样才能纠正你的胡说八道
just to correct your bullshit.
那你为什么对皮尔斯这么感兴趣
So why are you so into Pierce?
我只是觉得 我们懂新闻 你明白的 做我们擅长的事情
I just think we know news, you know, stay in our lane.
你喜欢吗
Do you like it?
我他妈的爱死了
I fuckin' love it.
是的 我的意思是
Yeah, I mean,
合并效果会很好
synergies are great.
没错 大屠杀和裁员 诸如此类的屁事
Exactly. Carnage and layoffs, all that shit.
...不好意思 这个电话很私密
...Pardon me. This is private.
你好
Hello.
我就是罗曼
You have Roman.
你好吗
How are you?
是吗 那会怎么样
Yeah? And what would that be?
好啊 那我们... 那我们坚持下去吧
Great. Let's...Let's stay across that.
感谢您提供的信息
Thank you for the information.
再聊 谢谢你告诉我 再见
Talk soon. Thanks for letting me know. Bye.
好消息吗
Good news?
-是的 当然  -嘿 拜托 伙计
- Yeah, sure. - Hey, come on, man.
怎么回事
What was that?
别他妈管了 是公关的事情 不是什么大事
Just fuckin' leave it. It's a PR thing. It was nothing.
看着我
Look at me.
我了解你 说吧 你满口谎言
I know you. Come on. You're full of shit.
嗯 我也了解你
Well, I know you.
你他妈的为什么在皮尔斯的事情上撒谎
Why the fuck are you lying about Pierce?
我们现在准备开车了
We are ready to do the drive now.
好的 走吧
All right. Go on.
我们去谋杀一只吓得要死的哺乳动物吧
Let's go murder a terrified mammal.
好吧
Okay.
我们是非常差劲的猎人
We're such shitty hunters
我们只是在射桶里的猪
that we're just shooting piggies in a barrel.
还不如直接朝猪扔手榴弹
Might as well just throw a grenade at the pigs.
等等 等等
Hold on. Hold on.
很好
Good.
-谢谢  -谢谢
- Thank you. - Thank you.
-嘿 听着 卡尔  -怎么了
- Hey, listen, Karl. - Yeah?
我在想...想和你聊聊
I was thinking I... It would be nice to have a chat,
因为我是... 我想聊一个对你来说有可能很棒的举措
'cause I was... about a possible cool move for you?
-对了 格丽  -怎么了
- Right. Gerri? - Yeah?
嗯 我们...我们想和你...聊聊 汤姆
Yeah. We... We wanted to have a...a chat with you, Tom.
我不知道你对皮尔斯收购计划的看法
I don't know how you feel about Pierce,
但是 我们有些人 有一点点疑惑
but a few of us were having a few doubts.
-好的  -是的
- Okay. - Yeah.
好吧 嗯 这很有趣 这... 真的很聪明
Okay. Well, that's interesting. That's... That's really smart.
你为什么不... 为什么不提出来呢
Why don't you... Why don't you raise it?
好吧 不过 我们也认为和他谈谈
Okay. Although we also thought it could be good
-对你有好处  -是的
- for you to talk to him? - Yeah.
好吧 好的 不过...
Okay. All right. Although...
如果是由值得信赖的老部下来提
wouldn't it be better if it came from
-会不会...   -对
- old, trusted... - Right.
-...更好呢  -那样很明智
- ...colleagues? - That's smart.
卡尔 这很有意思 我们应该这样做吗
Karl, that's interesting. Should we do it?
那样做很棒
That would be cool.
其实 由谁亲口说出来不是什么大不了的事
It's not a big deal, really, who actually says it.
我觉得你是家人 他对待家人的方式确实不一样
I guess you are family, and he does treat family differently.
是的 不一样 当然
Yeah. No, sure.
不过 他确实叫过我一次"基督山贱婊"
Although, he did once call me "The Cunt of Monte Cristo".
那是... 那是在逗弄你
That's... That was joshing.
在某种程度上 这也证明了你们之间的亲近
In a way, that's a testament to your closeness.
-某种程度上  -他喜欢你 汤姆
- In a way... - He likes you, Tom.
他喜欢你 你是个脑子聪明 口齿伶俐
He likes you. You're a fine mind, articulate,
-强有力的领导者  -我口齿伶俐吗
- strong leader. - I'm articulate?
你知道吗 你们太客气了
You're so kind, you know.
事实上 我非常受宠若惊
In fact, I'm so flattered,
我他妈就直接朝着机枪阵冲过去了
I'll just fucking walk right into the machine gun nest.
另外 我和小西谈过
Also, I've spoken to Shiv
我知道她让你去跟他说
and I know she asked you to talk to him.
-你和小西谈过吗  -如果你不这样做
- You spoke to Shiv? - And if you don't,
要是她问起来 你说怎么办
and she asks, yeah?
汤姆 英雄就是这样诞生的 在战场上
That's where heroes are born, Tom. On the battlefield.
英雄通常也是死在战场上的 格丽
It's also commonly where they're killed, Gerri.
我们会支持你的
We'll back you up.
洛根 我跟你说...
Well, Logan, look...
我不想扫大家的兴 但是我必须说出来
I hate to be a party pooper, but I have poop.
皮尔斯家族银行打电话告诉我
The Pierce family bank have called to say
说他们知道了你要收购他们的消息
the family got word that you were on maneuvers.
他们被吓坏了 我们得马上回来
It freaked them out. We need to back right off.
收购计划应该是精心设计的
This was supposed to be choreographed.
这就像一只狗穿着旱冰鞋
That's about as choreographed
被人操一样精心设计
as a dog getting fucked on roller-skates.
有人泄漏了消息吗
Was there a leak?
我们都很谨慎 可能是意外漏的口风
It was cagey. It might have been accidental.
不 不 不 这不是意外
No. No, no. This was no accident.
有人想阻止我收购
Someone's trying to fuck me.
还有谁知道 没人
Who knew? No one.
是这里的某个人
It's someone here.
我的篮子里有条他妈的蛇[内奸]
I've got snakes in the fucking basket.
你想让我再看一遍
Do you want me to go down the list
-其他收购目标的名单吗  -不
- of other acquisition targets? - No!
我就要皮尔斯
I want Pierce!
你回去 找到另外一种方式
Get back to the city. Find another way.
这些混蛋想要扼杀我的收购计划 该死的侏儒
Some of these fuckers are trying to kill this. Fucking pygmies!
他妈的虱子
Fucking lice!
你搞定了吗
大家过得还好吗
How we all doing?
花公司的钱花得都很开心吧
All havin' a nice time on the company dollar?
格丽 你没事吧 你看起来很累
Gerri, you all right? You look tired.
不 我...我很好 谢谢
No, I'm... I'm good, thanks.
好 因为我明早想要皮尔斯养老金的资料
Good. 'Cause I want the Pierce pension options first thing.
对 那... 或许我应该走了
Right, so... so I should probably go.
留下来 你知道的 我们需要鼓舞士气
Stay. You know, we need to boost morale.
好的 好的 是啊 我能感觉到士气在上升
Okay, great. Yeah. I can feel it rising.
洛根 只是...预警一下 家人...家人的预警
Logan? Just a... a heads up. A fam... A family heads up,
只是...只是想让你知道
just to... just to let you know
我一会可能会说些话
that in a moment I might say something,
但是不要担心 因为我说的不是真心话
but not to worry, 'cause it's not real.
好吗
Okay?
-什么...   -只是 主要内容是
- Wh... - Just, headline is
我一会要说些话 但是不要理会我的话
I'm gonna say something, but disregard it.
我觉得 大家可能把我看作是领导
I think that people think of me as a kind of leader.
因为他们想提出一个问题
Because there was an issue that they wanted raised,
但是 你不要有这种印象
but don't you be under the impression
就是... 我说我反对什么就是我真的反对什么 好吗
that... that I'm against what I'll say I'm against. Okay?
-皮尔斯  -什么
- Pierce. - What?
皮尔斯 大家反对这个计划
Pierce. People are against it.
但是 那是因为他们害怕
But that's because they're scared.
但是 他们觉得我很勇敢
But they think of me as kind of brave,
如果需要我勇敢 我会勇敢 但是我并不需要 所以...
which I would be if I needed to be, but I don't, so...
好吗
Good.
一起干个杯
A toast.
音乐家们
Musicians?
声音小点
Pianissimo.
为我们的顶级团队干杯
To our top team.
顶级团队
Top team.
再来一杯 再来一杯 倒满 倒满
And again. And again. Fill her up, fill her up.
吃点 每个人都吃点 多吃点 多喝点
Eat, everybody. Eat. And drink.
来吧 这是派对 不是吗
Come on now. It's a party, isn't it?
来吧 喂 雷 你要去哪儿
Come on. Hey! Ray, where you going?
小个便
To take a leak.
你知道的 我们团结一致
You know. We're all sticking together.
如果您要撒尿 那就撒在桶里
If you need a leak, piss in a bucket.
我的意思是... 我们现在都关起来了
I mean... we're locking down.
没关系 我们都是好朋友 是啊
It's all right. We're all pals here. Yeah.
对
Right.
我的天啦 雷 我是在让你憋着
Jesus Christ, Ray. I'm pullin' your pisser.
把那个桶放下来 你个恶心的混蛋
Put that bucket down, you disgusting bastard.
我的天啦
My God.
我们在哪儿找的这些家伙
Where do we find 'em?
音乐家们 谢谢 继续演奏吧
Musicians! Thank you. Again.
很好 食物很不错
Good. The food.
坐吧 坐吧
Sit, sit.
那你是做什么的 重要的工作吗
So what do you do? Something important?
不 不是
No. Nope.
好吧 有一天你会的
Well, you will one day.
但愿如此
Here's hopin'.
我得打个电话
I gotta make a call.
打给嫉妒的男朋友吗
Jealous boyfriend?
不是
No.
只是一个为我工作的人
Just a guy who works for me.
-周六也工作啊  -他最好是在工作
- Working on a Saturday? - He better be.
听起来你对他太苛刻了
Sounds like you're riding him hard.
好吧 也许他喜欢这样
Well, maybe he likes it.
你是在和我调情吗
Are you flirting with me?
你的调情让我裤子都湿了
Your flirt got all over my pants.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
嘿 汤姆 只是了解下你和他说了没有
Hey, Tom. Just checking you talked to him.
士兵 别让我失望
Don't let me down, soldier.
小西
Shiv?
我是...
It's...
传媒大亨洛根·罗伊的长子
Connor Roy, eldest son of media mogul,
康纳·罗伊挑战
山姆大叔
-康纳·罗伊  -我的天啦
- Logan Roy... - Jesus Christ.
康纳·罗伊挑战
山姆大叔
... 宣称 他宁愿入狱
...announced his intention to go to prison,
也不愿意按照当前水平
rather than pay federal income tax
缴纳联邦所得税
at the current level.
嘿 康纳·罗伊
Hey. Connor Roy.
不过 他看起来很可爱
He looks cute, though.
尝起来就像... 我猜野猪肉尝起来像鸡肉
It tastes... I guess boar tastes like chicken.
不 野猪是野猪 野猪是猪
No! Boar is boar. Boar is piggy.
试试那个黑色的...
Try that black...
-血肠...   -来吧 各位
- blood sausage... - Come on, everyone.
我们应该过得很开心才对 喝起来
We're supposed to be having a nice time! Drink!
汤姆 现在是时候了 汤姆
Tom. Now's the time, Tom.
-你觉得呢  -是的
- You think? - Yeah.
付了很多钱的
Paid enough.
祝一杯酒... 弗兰克 你想来祝酒吗
A toast....Frank. You wanna?
好吧
Okay.
... 不好意思
...'Scuse me.
-为老朋友干杯  - 贴心 为老朋友干杯
- To old friends. - Lovely. To old friends.
你为什么要来 弗兰克
Why'd you come, Frank?
什么 ... 来这里吗
W... Here?
因为你邀请了我
Because you invited me.
不是为了侦查你的某个自以为是的老朋友吗
Not on a recon for some of your old stuck up pals?
洛根 我们老了 我尽量不让围栏破碎[友谊破裂]
Logan, we're old. I try not to leave fences broken.
你就是个他妈的马屁精
You're a fucking creep.
你说什么
Excuse me?
我的意思是 你... 你去找了三份工作
I mean you... you went for three jobs,
一个都没有得到
you didn't get any of them.
你的葡萄园就是个报废的烂货
Your vineyard was a write-off.
而现在 你的花瓶女朋友
And now your trophy girlfriend
正在巴勒莫给某个服务员口交
is sucking some waiter's dick in Palermo,
所以现在你才爬回来
so now you've come crawling back,
像一只他妈的蛆虫
like a fucking worm.
我其实蛮高兴他现在回来了
I'm actually kinda glad he's back now.
这是怎么回事
What's happening here?
小肯
Ken.
跟他说 汤姆 就现在
Talk to him, Tom. Now.
滚开
Fuck off.
有人和米歇尔·潘特西尔谈过话
Someone has spoken to Michelle Pantsil.
我们这艘船上有老鼠[内奸]
We've got rats on this ship.
还有皮尔斯的计划
And Pierce.
这是怎么回事
What's going on?
谁在支持我
Who's got my back?
谁是真的在支持我
Who's really behind me?
有谁吗 对不起 有谁想坦白承认吗
Anyone? Excuse me. Anyone wanna own up?
有谁想供出内奸吗
Anyone wanna rat out a rat?
悉德
Cyd?
你是老鼠吗
Are you a rat?
不是
No.
-你呢  -不 我不是
- How about you? - No. I'm not.
卡尔 你有事要告诉我吗
Karl, you got something to tell me?
比如呢
Such as?
我不知道 比如 当地的妓院在哪里
I don't know, where the local whorehouse is.
好吧 这个我不知道
Well, I don't know about that.
那你家的老太太知道吗
Does your old lady know about that?
不
No.
你知道吗....
You know....
她知道我是个浪荡子
She knows that I'm something of a Libertine,
-但是... 好的  -那... 那是承认了吗
- but... Okay. - Is... is that a yes?
我... 我们要不要开免提然后问问她
Sh... Should we get her on the speaker phone and ask her?
好了 洛根 拜托 什么他妈的鬼
Come on. Logan, please. What the fuck?
每个人 都把手机放在桌子上
Everyone, phones on the table.
公司和私人的都拿出来 快点 手机放在桌子上
Company and private. Come on. Phones on the table now.
这真的有必要吗
Is that really necessary?
我甚至不确定这样做... 这样做合法吗
I'm not even sure it's... it's legal
-要求大家...   -嗯 这个嘛
- to demand people... - Yeah, well,
我们要开始谈实质性问题了
we're getting down to brass fucking tacks.
汤姆 你和你那脆弱的自我跟潘特西尔谈过吗
Tom, did you and your fragile ego talk to Pantsil?
不 没有 先生
No. No, sir.
没有 洛根 不如我们换个话题谈谈策略
No. Logan, why don't we switch to strategy?
这有个策略 汤姆
Here's a strategy, Tom:
不如你先安静下来 直到你过来告诉我
Why don't you pipe down till you come and tell me
我就要有孙子了
I've got a grandson coming?
或者 你一直在放空枪[暗示没有生育能力]
Or are you shooting blanks?
-卡尔  -嗯
- Karl? - Yeah?
你喜欢收购皮尔斯的交易吗
Do you like the, the Pierce deal?
我喜欢 我喜欢 是的 没错
I do. I do, yes. Yeah. Yeah.
放屁
Bullshit.
地板上的野猪
Boar on the floor.
嘿
Hey!
-好吧  -这是个游戏
- Okay. - It's a game.
在角落里 那边 站去那里
In the corner, over there. Stand there.
去 去 去 快去
Go, go, go, go, go.
好的
All right.
汤姆
Tom?
-我吗  -是的
- Me? - Yeah.
-皮尔斯吗  -是的
- Pierce? - Yeah.
嗯 有很多...
Well, there's a lot of...
因素 ...
factors, and...
但是 我个人... 我喜欢 我喜欢这个计划
but yes. I personally... I like it. I like it.
去那边 地板上的野猪
Boar on the floor over there.
格丽 站起来
Gerri, stand up.
站起来
Stand up!
皮尔斯
Pierce?
告诉不了你 告诉不了你 不知道
Couldn't tell you. Couldn't tell you. Don't know.
-你以前玩过吗  -没有
- Have you played it before? - No!
嗯 实际上 我...
Well, actually, I...
说实话 我... 我有一些疑虑
To be perfectly honest, I've... I've had a few doubts.
诚实
Honesty.
你们看到了吗 各位 你们看到了吗
You see, everybody? Do you see?
诚实
Honesty.
格雷格 站起来
Greg, stand up.
你有收到我哥哥的任何命令吗
Did you get any orders from my brother,
我那个他妈的"大草原的良知"哥哥
the fuckin' Conscience of the Prairies?
-我吗  -是的
- Me? - Yeah.
我...没有...
I... don't......
嗯 因为我...我...
Yeah. I... 'Cause I...
我也有一些疑虑
I've had some doubts too.
他妈的持怀疑态度的人 去那边
Fucking doubter. Over there.
但是规则是 如果说实话 就可以得到豁免啊
But the rules are that you're spared if you tell the truth,
-而我刚刚说了实话  -噢 还有规则啊
- and I just told you the truth! - There are rules?
-是啊  -你知道吗 格雷格
- Right? - Do you know something, Greg?
没有他妈的规则 去那边
There are no fucking rules. Over there.
好吧
Okay.
罗曼
Roman!
我真的很喜欢 爸
I like it for real, Dad,
-我想帮忙...   -你他妈站起来
- I wanna help... - Stand the fuck up.
好吧
Okay.
肯德尔接到了传记作者的电话
Kendall took a call from the biographer.
我们都接到电话了 罗曼
We all got a call, Rome.
好的 是的 但是你... 看 他看上去好像
Okay, yes, but you... See, he seemed like
真的想和她谈谈
he wanted to actually talk to her.
为了帮爸爸让你露原形
To smoke you out for Dad.
什么 去你妈的 你要让我露什么原形
What? Fuck you. Why'd you get to smoke me out?
是我让你露原形
I was smokin' you out.
你为什么不跟我们说说你的神秘电话
Why don't you tell us about your mystery call?
那通电话吗
The phone call?
噢 是弗兰克打的
Yeah. It was Frank.
他本来打算打给你
He meant to call you.
他想知道 推翻爸的计划是否还在进行
He wants to know if the plan to overthrow Dad is still happening.
有人在阻止收购皮尔斯
Someone spiked Pierce.
是你们哪个猪猡干的
Which one of you boars did it?
-汤姆  -怎么了
- Tom! - Yes?
坐在地上
Sit on the floor!
很好玩的
It's fun.
-说真的吗  -是的 这是个游戏
- Seriously? - Yeah, it's a game!
-地板上的野猪  - 我真的... 我觉得...
- Boar on the floor! - I really... I feel...
趴下
Get down!
地板上的野猪
Boar on the floor.
地板上的野猪 肯德尔 组织一下
Boar on the floor. Kendall, bring the troops.
地板上的野猪
Boar on the floor.
-趴下  - 地板上的野猪
- Get down! - Boar on the floor.
格雷格 趴在地板上 扮野猪
Greg! On the floor, boar.
来吧 弗兰克
Come on, Frank!
我为什么在这
Why am I in this?
格雷格 我他妈怎么知道
How the fuck would I know, Greg?
你觉得我对此有合理的解释吗
You think I have a rational explanation for this?
弗兰克 喂猪 你是嘉宾
Frank! Feed the piggies, guests of honor!
就是这样 地板上的野猪
That's it. Boar on the floor!
地板上的野猪
Boar on the floor!
为你的香肠哼哼 猪猡们
Oink for your sausages, piggies.
为你的香肠哼哼 猪猡们 哼哼
Oink for your sausages, piggies. Oink.
老天啊
Jesus Christ.
-汤姆 为你的香肠哼哼 哼哼  -哼哼
- Oink for your sausage, Tom. Oink. - Oink.
不
No.
不 哼得一点也没有诚意
No half-hearted oink.
-我不会这么做的  -哼哼 哼哼 哼哼
- I'm not doing it. - Oink, oink, oink.
数到三
On the count of three,
最后一个吃香肠的小猪就是内奸
the last piggy to eat a sausage is the mole.
这似乎不是一个很好的系统...
That doesn't seem like a very good system...
谁跟潘特西尔谈过话
Who spoke to Pantsil?
求你了
Please.
喂
Hey!
爬成一圈 闭上眼睛
Crawl in a circle and close your eyes.
三...
Three...
格雷格 哼哼
Greg, oink.
二...
Two...
一...
One...
吃香肠 汤姆
Eat the sausage, Tom!
我拿到了
I got it!
从他手里抢过来
Take it out of his hand!
加油啊
Come on.
卡尔偷了我的香肠
Karl stole my sausage.
太他妈慢了 我会把你的安慰奖给你
Too effing slow. I'll get you your booby prize.
吃光 猪仔
Eat up, piggies.
我相信他说的是 "吃光 猪仔"
I believe he said "Eat up, piggies."
我想看你们这些傻逼猪仔吃香肠 吃啊
I wanna see you little piggy fucks eat. Eat it.
赔偿 你他妈的呆逼
Indemnification, you fuckin' dummy.
你... 你他妈来真的吗 你多大了
Wh... You fucking serious? How old are you?
把我他妈的手机还给我
Give me back my fucking phone.
-你在隐藏什么  -你在... 隐藏...什么
- What are you hiding? - What are you... Wh... Hiding?
什么都没隐藏 把我他妈的手机还给我
Nothing. Give me back my fucking phone.
-你的密码是多少  -你他妈来真的吗
- What's your code? - Are you fucking serious?
-是的 你的...   -我的密码吗 我的密码是
- Yeah. What's your... - My code? My code is,
操你妈... 什么
fuck you... What?
好的 给你了 好吗 开心了吗 里面什么都没有
Okay, you got it. All right? Happy? There's nothing in there.
嘿 你想喝这个吗
Hey, do you wanna hit this?
这其实只是我留在排水管里的
It's actually just some resin I left in the downpipe
-一些树脂  -美味啊
- in the bowl, I'm afraid. - Yum. No.
-谢谢  -好的
- Thank you. - All right.
那 没有电视吗
So, no TV?
你...你是个只玩笔记本电脑的人吗
You a... You a laptop guy?
对 没电视
Nah, no screens.
不... 不看新闻吗
No...No news?
我不看新闻
I don't follow the news.
不看 现在这时代 真正的新闻
No, these days, actually the real news
实际上是来自喜剧演员
comes from comedians.
你接下来要说的话不会让我发疯的
I'm not crazy to hear the next thing you're gonna say.
我可以直接吻你吗
Can I just kiss you?
坦白说 我现在有一段关系
Full disclosure, I am in a relationship,
不过 是一种开放的关系
but it's an open relationship.
听起来很波希米亚 很复杂
It sounds bohemian and complicated,
但实际上很简单
but actually it's pretty simple.
你...你有什么问题吗
You...Do you have any, questions?
-我觉得我没什么问题  -太棒了
- I don't think so. - Great.
-嘿 对不起 -把我的电话给我
- Hey, I'm sorry. - Give me my phone.
把我他妈的电话还给我
Give me my fucking phone.
你... 抓着我的... 你喜欢摸我吗
You're... Grab my... You like touching me?
抓我他妈的鸡巴啊 我他妈玩死你 你狗日的
Grab my fucking balls, I will drop you, cocksucker.
没错 你看到一个电话号码 那又怎么样
Yeah, you see a phone number, so what?
所有人都必须有奖品
All must have prizes.
里面有什么 奖品是什么
What's in there? What's the prize?
嘿 爸
Hey, Dad?
是罗曼 罗曼和皮尔斯谈过
It was Roman. Roman talked to Pierce.
他接到了娜奥米·皮尔斯的电话
He, took a call from Naomi Pierce.
爸
Dad.
罗曼 有人收买你了吗
Roman, did someone get at you?
爸 我没有背叛你
Dad, I didn't betray you.
那今天这个电话是什么意思
Then what's this call from today?
-你为什么跟她通话  -拜托 伙计
- Why are you talking to her? - Come on, man.
我不是想搞砸这笔交易
I wasn't trying to fuck the deal,
我是想达成这笔交易
I was trying to land the deal.
我是想帮忙 我...
I was trying to help. I...
我想着这会是一个很好的惊喜
I thought it would be a nice surprise.
罗曼...
Roman...
你是个白痴
you're a moron.
他要去当地板上的野猪吗
Boar on the floor?
-我就随便说说  -操你妈
- I'm just saying. - Fuck you.
我不是白痴 爸爸
I'm not a moron, Dad.
一加仑牛奶多少钱
How much is a gallon of milk?
什么
What?
-一加仑牛奶多少钱  -我不知道
- How much is a gallon of milk? - I don't know.
我的意思是 谁他妈知道 爸爸 实际上没有人知道
I mean, who the fuck knows, Dad? Literally no one knows.
-谁在乎呢  -雷
- Who gives a shit? - Ray!
一加仑牛奶多少钱
How much is a gallon of milk?
普通牛奶 还是...
I mean, like regular milk, or...
我身边都是些阴险的毒蛇和该死的白痴
I am surrounded by snakes and fucking morons.
你们他妈的就是一群绣花枕头
You're a bunch of silk-stocking fucks!
谁支持我收购皮尔斯
Who backs me on Pierce?
谁
Who?
他们都不支持 爸爸
None of them do, Dad.
他们都反对
They're all against it.
好吗 卡尔在说谎
Okay? Karl's lying,
雷在说谎 格丽在耍两面派
Ray's lying, Gerri's playing both sides.
好吧...
Well...
宣布一下
Here's news.
我们要收购它
We are going after it.
而且...
And what's more...
我必胜
I will win.
嘿 早上好
Hey, morning.
你怎么样
How you doing'?
真棒的夜晚 我不知道你们怎么样
Quite a night. I don't know about you guys,
但是我喝多了 什么都记不起来了
but I had one too many. I can't remember anything.
早上好 汤姆
Morning, Tom.
-要香肠吗  -不 谢谢
- Sausage? - No, thank you.
-汤姆 我要吃你的香肠  -我相信你会的 悉德
- I'll eat your sausage, Tom. - I'm sure you will, Cyd.
你在期待什么
What you were expecting?
没期待什么
Not really.
他说他提出让你官复原职
He said he offered you your job back.
是啊
Yeah.
我在考虑
I'm considering.
为什么
Why?
我需要钱雇个人去巴勒莫杀个人
I need money to pay someone to kill a guy in Palermo.
小孩需要鞋子 飞蛾要扑火...
Baby needs shoes, moth to a flame...
我也说不清
I don't know.
嘿
Hey.
早上好 早上好
Morning, morning. Morning.
-要咖啡吗  -不 跟往常一样
- Coffee? - Nah. The usual.
来吧 坐我旁边
Come, join me.
如果昨晚有点过于荒诞了 我很抱歉
I'm, sorry if last night got a little bit fruity.
但是 你知道的...
But, you know...
时差 药物 恶作剧 对吧 对吧
jet-lag, meds, horseplay, right? Right?
时差...
The jet-lag...
我也是这样
I get the same way.
我刚才听说是谁和米歇尔·潘特西尔谈过话了
I just heard who Michelle Pantsil talked to.
是老莫
It was Mo.
狗屎一块
Piece of shit!
我还和玛丽亚谈过 老莫昨晚去世了
I also talked to Maria. Mo passed away last night.
什么
What?
老莫现在死了吗
Mo now?
老天
Jesus.
向玛丽亚带去我的...
Give Maria my...
慰问 我...
condolences. I...
我...事实上 派山姆过来 我们把老莫的电子邮件破解了
I... In fact, send Sam over. Let's crack his email.
我他妈想知道他一直在瞎逼逼什么
I want to know what the fuck he's been saying.
老莫
Mo.
-嘿 格雷格  -嘿 汤姆
- Hey, Greg. - Hey, Tom.
谢谢 伙计
Thanks, man.
不... 谢谢你 我可以自己倒 谢谢
No... Thank you. I can do that. Thanks.
他们... 他们在等你
They... They're waiting for you.
-所以呢  -所以 快点
- So? - So, hurry up.
所以 弗兰克又他妈的是我的保姆了
So Frank's my fucking babysitter again.
爸爸要杀了我 他正在割我的蛋蛋
Dad is killing me. He's cutting my fucking balls off.
我扣不上我的纽扣
I can't do my buttons.
它们他妈的是肥皂做的吗
Are they fucking made of soap?
过来
Come here.
你知道吗 如果我能突然移动
You know, if I were capable of any sudden movement,
我现在会扑到你身上
I would totally pounce on you right now.
-是吗  -是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
实际上我听到过很多这样的话
I actually hear that a lot.
通常是九十多岁的男人说的
Usually from men in their nineties.
那个扣子你得自己扣
You have to do that one.
你还好吗
How are you doing?
太糟了
Terrible.
非常... 糟糕
Pretty... awful.
顺便说一下 我在责怪塔比莎
I'm blaming Tabitha, by the way.
这是她的想法
It was her idea.
下次你需要商业建议时
Next time you need business advice,
问一个知道自己在说什么的人
ask someone who knows what they're talking about.
-什么 你吗  - 是的 比如我
- What, you? - Yeah. Like me.
好吧 好吧 我要怎么做才能让他认真对待我
Okay. Well, how do I get him to take me seriously?
长点胡子 读点期刊吗
Grow a moustache and read the Journal?
我他妈的会去做的
I'll fuckin' do it.
好吧 罗曼 如果你想知道...
Okay, Roman, if you wanna know...
... 那就参加管理培训计划 从底层做起
...do the management training program, ground floor.
去屠宰场工作
Work at a slaughterhouse.
了解一加仑牛奶的价格
Learn the price of a gallon of milk.
他妈的为什么对牛奶这么痴迷
What the fuck is his obsession with milk?
你知道谁喝牛奶吗 小猫和变态
You know who drinks milk? Kittens and perverts.
嘿 洛根
Hey, Logan.
皮尔斯的总裁瑞亚·贾雷尔
Pierce's CEO, Rhea Jarrell,
发了封电子邮件 说她听说了你的方案
emailed saying she heard about your approach.
她可以帮我们
She can help us.
那... 你能把她的头放在盘子上拿来给我吗
So... can you bring me her head on a platter?
我能把她的头
I can bring you her head
连同她身体的其余部分一起带给你
attached to the rest of her body.
好
Good.
更好
Even better.
干得好 弗兰克
Good work, Frank.
很好
Great.
嘿
Hey.
怎么样
How was it?
非常...
It was pretty...
-非常艰辛... 实际上 是的  -是吗
- pretty tough... actually, yeah. - Yeah?
有人告诉你了吗
Anybody fill you in?
没有 发生... 发生什么事了
No. Wh... What happened?
你爸爸有点暴躁
Your dad was a little peppery.
对不起 汤姆
I'm sorry, Tom.
也许你让我去做的事情并不完全好
Maybe it wasn't totally great what you sent me to do.
这和我想做的事情正好相反
Which is kind of the opposite of what I wanted to do.
是吗
Yeah.
我的意思是...
I mean...
-我们是一个团队 对吧  -是的
- we're a team, right? - Yeah.
但是我...我不想当个混蛋
But I... I don't wanna be a dick,
但是 也许我应该多参与一些团队战术
but maybe I should have a bit more input into team tactics.
是啊 当然 当然
Yeah. Sure. Of course.
谢谢
Thanks.
那 你周末过得怎么样
So, how was your weekend?
-我吗  -是的 有什么想说的吗
- Me? - Yeah. Anything to report?
是啊 好吧
Yeah. Okay.
你想知道吗
Do you want to know?
我不... 也许以后吧
I don't... maybe later.
过来
Come here.
喂 爸
Hey, Dad.
你好 小可爱
Hello, Pinkie.
对不起我错过了你的电话
Sorry I missed your call.
有很多事要处理
Had a lot to deal with.
木家具里出现了白蚁 叛乱分子
Termites in the woodwork. Insurgents.
是吗
Yeah?
哪里来的
Coming from where?
前排[亲近的人] 便宜的座位[低级别手下] 哪里都有
Front row, cheap seats, every-fucking-where.
反正我没有
Not from me.
你现在在做什么
What are you doing at the moment?
-闲着呢  -我们定个日子吧
- I'm free. - We'll set a date.
是时候让你参与进来了
It's time to bring you in.
ZIMUXIA.CN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
爸爸在开秘密会议
Dad's in a secret meeting,
而我在这里闲坐着
and I'm in here with a coloring book.
怎么了 格丽
What's going on, Gerri?
我想要皮尔斯
I want Pierce,
但是 只有我们快点见面才能搞定
but it only works if we meet fast.
瑞亚 她来了
Rhea, she's coming.
那个家族信任她 你让她上船
The family trusts her, you get her on board,
意义重大
that's huge.
我代表皮尔斯家族 带来一条消息
On behalf of the Pierce family, I have a message.
怎么回事
What's that?
-什么 什么  -先生 请跟我来 是的
- What, what? - Sir, please follow me, yeah.
对不起 对不起
Excuse me, excuse me.
等等 肯德尔在哪 他安全吗
Wait, where's Kendall, is he safe?